class BaybayinQuizQuestions {

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> baybayinCharacters = [
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin character translate to "ka"?',
      'options': ['ᜃ', 'ᜁ', 'ᜇ', 'ᜈ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜃ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin character translate to "ta"?',
      'options': ['ᜆ᜔', 'ᜅ', 'ᜆ', 'ᜎ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜆ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman alphabets translate to "ᜑ"?',
      'options': ['he', 'ha', 'hi', 'hu'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ha',
    },
        {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman alphabets translate to "ᜊ"?',
      'options': ['bu', 'ba', 'be', 'bo'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ba',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Baybayin characters to spell "mama" (mother).',
      'options': ['ᜋᜒ', 'ᜋ᜔', 'ᜋ', 'ᜋᜓ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜋ', 'ᜋ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Baybayin characters to spell "lola" (grandmother).',
      'options': ['ᜎᜒ', 'ᜎ', 'ᜎᜓ', 'ᜎ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜎᜓ', 'ᜎ'],
    },
        {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Roman Alphabets to spell "ᜉᜉ"',
      'options': ['pu', 'pe','pa','po'],
      'correctAnswer': ['pa', 'pa'],
    },
        {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Roman Alphabets to spell "ᜆᜒᜆ"',
      'options': ['ta', 'to', 'tu', 'ti'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ti', 'ta'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin character for "ka".',
      'character': 'ᜃ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin character for "nga".',
      'character': 'ᜅ',
    },
  ];

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> twoSyllableWords = [
    {    
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "lupa" (earth)?',
      'options': ['ᜎᜉᜓ', 'ᜎᜓᜉ', 'ᜎᜓᜉᜒ', 'ᜎ᜔ᜉ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜎᜓᜉ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "puso" (heart)?',
      'options': ['ᜃᜋᜌ᜔', 'ᜊᜓᜊᜓ', 'ᜋᜆ', 'ᜉᜓᜐᜓ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜉᜓᜐᜓ',
    },    
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜁᜎᜏ᜔"?',
      'options': ['ilow', 'eliw', 'ilaw', 'elaw'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ilaw',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜊᜆᜓ"?',
      'options': ['bato', 'bata', 'buto', 'butu'],
      'correctAnswer': 'bato',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Baybayin characters to spell "gabi" (night)',
      'options': ['ᜄ', 'ᜊᜒ', 'ᜄᜓ', 'ᜊᜓ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜄ', 'ᜊᜒ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Baybayin characters to spell "buto" (bone).',
      'options': ['ᜊ', 'ᜆ', 'ᜊᜓ', 'ᜆᜓ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜊᜓ', 'ᜆᜓ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Roman Alphabets to spell "ᜋᜆ" ',
      'options': ['ma', 'mu', 'ta', 'to'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ma', 'ta'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Choose which Roman Alphabets to spell "ᜊᜑ" ',
      'options': ['hu', 'ba', 'ha', 'bo'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ba', 'ha'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "damo" (grass)',
      'character': 'ᜇᜋᜓ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "kubo" (hut).',
      'character': 'ᜃᜓᜊ',
    },
  ];

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> threeSyllableWords = [
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "dalawa" (two)?',
      'options': ['ᜀᜉᜆ᜔', 'ᜆᜆᜎᜓ', 'ᜇᜎᜏ', 'ᜎᜒᜋ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜇᜎᜏ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "lalaki" (man)?',
      'options': ['ᜊᜊᜁ', 'ᜎᜎᜃᜒ', 'ᜉᜆᜌ᜔', 'ᜎᜃᜇ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜎᜎᜃᜒ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜋᜐᜌ"?',
      'options': ['masuyo', 'malungkot', 'masaya', 'mosaya'],
      'correctAnswer': 'masaya',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜋᜆᜒᜉᜒᜇ᜔"?',
      'options': ['matipid', 'matupod', 'matupid', 'motupod'],
      'correctAnswer': 'matipid',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "tatlo" (three)',
      'options': ['ᜆ', 'ᜆ᜔', 'ᜆᜓ', 'ᜎᜓ', 'ᜎ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜆ', 'ᜆ᜔', 'ᜎᜓ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "mataba" (fat)',
      'options': ['ᜋ', 'ᜆ᜔', 'ᜊ', 'ᜋ᜔', 'ᜆ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜋ', 'ᜆ', 'ᜊ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜋᜎᜃᜒ" ',
      'options': ['ma', 'lo', 'ki', 'la', 'ka'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ma', 'la', 'ki'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜉᜌᜉ" ',
      'options': ['po', 'ya', 'yi', 'pa'],
      'correctAnswer': ['pa', 'ya', 'pa'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "babae" (woman)',
      'character': 'ᜊᜊᜁ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "maganda" (beautiful)',
      'character': 'ᜋᜄᜈ᜔ᜇ',
    },
  ];

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> fourSyllableWords = [
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "paaralan" (school)?',
      'options': ['ᜉᜋᜒᜎᜌ', 'ᜋᜄᜓᜎᜅ᜔', 'ᜉᜀᜇᜎᜈ᜔', 'ᜃᜁᜊᜒᜄᜈ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜉᜀᜇᜎᜈ᜔',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "mahalaga" (important)?',
      'options': ['ᜋᜑᜎᜃᜒᜆ', 'ᜋᜑᜎᜄ', 'ᜋᜑᜊᜅ', 'ᜋᜑᜐ'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜋᜑᜎᜄ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜋᜉᜄ᜔ᜇᜐᜎ᜔" ?',
      'options': ['mapagdasal', 'mahalaga', 'maalaga', 'pagdadasal'],
      'correctAnswer': 'mapagdasal',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜋᜐᜓᜈᜓᜇᜒᜈ᜔" ?',
      'options': ['mabusisi', 'masunurin', 'susunurin', 'malakasan'],
      'correctAnswer': 'masunurin',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "alapaap" (cloud)',
      'options': ['ᜉ', 'ᜀᜉ᜔', 'ᜀ', 'ᜎ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜀ', 'ᜎ', 'ᜉ', 'ᜀᜉ᜔'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "kaalaman" (knowledge)',
      'options': ['ᜋ', 'ᜈ᜔', 'ᜎ', 'ᜃ', 'ᜀ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜃ', 'ᜀ', 'ᜎ', 'ᜋ', 'ᜈ᜔'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜋᜆᜎᜒᜈᜓ" (intelligent)',
      'options': ['ta', 'li', 'ma', 'no'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ma', 'ta', 'li', 'no'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜐᜃ᜔ᜍᜒᜉᜒᜐ᜔ᜌᜓ" (intelligent)',
      'options': ['ri', 'pi', 'sak', 'syo'],
      'correctAnswer': ['sak', 'ri', 'pi', 'syo'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "matagal" (long time)',
      'character': 'ᜋᜆᜄᜎ᜔',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "marunong" (knowledgeable)',
      'character': 'ᜋᜇᜓᜈᜓᜅ᜔',
    },
  ];

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> fiveSyllableWords = [
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "katahimikan" (silence)?',
      'options': ['ᜋᜄᜓᜎᜅ᜔', 'ᜉᜋᜒᜎᜌ', 'ᜃᜉᜆᜒᜇ᜔', 'ᜃᜆᜑᜒᜋᜒᜃᜈ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜃᜆᜑᜒᜋᜒᜃᜈ᜔',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin word represents "kaligayahan" (happiness)?',
      'options': ['ᜃᜎᜓᜈᜓᜇᜈ᜔', 'ᜃᜆᜆᜄᜈ᜔', 'ᜃᜎᜒᜄᜌᜑᜈ᜔', 'ᜃᜉᜎᜒᜄᜒᜇᜈ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜃᜎᜒᜄᜌᜑᜈ᜔',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜃᜆᜎᜒᜈᜓᜑᜈ᜔"?',
      'options': ['kabutihan', 'katalinuhan', 'katarungan', 'katotohanan'],
      'correctAnswer': 'katalinuhan',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman Alphabet word represents "ᜃᜉᜌᜉᜀᜈ᜔"?',
      'options': ['kapayapaan', 'kapitalista', 'kapabayaan', 'kampeonato'],
      'correctAnswer': 'kapayapaan',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "interesado" (interested)',
      'options': ['ᜐ', 'ᜆᜒ', 'ᜇᜓ', 'ᜁᜈ᜔', 'ᜇᜒ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜁᜈ᜔', 'ᜆᜒ', 'ᜇᜒ', 'ᜐ', 'ᜇᜓ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin characters to spell "ekonomiko" (economic)',
      'options': ['ᜁ', 'ᜃᜓ', 'ᜈᜓ', 'ᜋᜒ'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜁ', 'ᜃᜓ', 'ᜈᜓ', 'ᜋᜒ', 'ᜃᜓ'], 
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜇᜓᜃᜓᜋᜒᜈ᜔ᜆᜇ᜔ᜌᜓ" ',
      'options': ['ku', 'tar', 'men', 'do', 'yo'],
      'correctAnswer': ['do', 'ku', 'men', 'tar', 'yo'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman Alphabet characters to spell "ᜂᜉᜓᜇ᜔ᜆᜓᜈᜒᜇᜇ᜔" ',
      'options': ['tu', 'ni', 'dad', 'o', 'por'],
      'correctAnswer': ['o','por','tu','ni','dad'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "kagandahan" (beauty)',
      'character': 'ᜃᜄᜈ᜔ᜇᜑᜈ᜔',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin word for "kalayaan" (freedom)',
      'character': 'ᜃᜎᜌᜀᜈ᜔',
    },
  ];

  static final List<Map<String, dynamic>> sentences = [
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin sentence means "Kumain ka na ba?" (Have you eaten yet?)',
      'options': [
        'ᜋᜄᜈ᜔ᜇ ᜀᜅ᜔ ᜀᜇᜏ᜔',
        'ᜃᜓᜋᜁᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜈ ᜊ',
        'ᜃᜓᜋᜓᜐ᜔ᜆ ᜃ',
        'ᜐᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜈᜅ᜔ᜄᜄᜎᜒᜅ᜔',
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜃᜓᜋᜁᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜈ ᜊ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Baybayin sentence means "Saan ka pupunta?" (Where are you going?)',
      'options': [
        'ᜉᜀᜎᜋ᜔ ᜈ',
        'ᜐᜀᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜈᜅ᜔ᜄᜄᜎᜒᜅ᜔',
        'ᜃᜓᜋᜁᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜈ ᜊ',
        'ᜐᜀᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜉᜓᜉᜓᜈ᜔ᜆ',
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'ᜐᜀᜈ᜔ ᜃ ᜉᜓᜉᜓᜈ᜔ᜆ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman alphabet sentence means "ᜉᜀᜎᜋ᜔ ᜈ"?',
      'options': [
        'salamat po',
        'paalam na',
        'kumusta ka',
        'mahal kita',
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'paalam na',
    },
    {
      'type': 'multiple_choice',
      'question': 'Which Roman alphabet sentence means "ᜃᜓᜋᜓᜐ᜔ᜆ ᜃ" ?',
      'options': [
        'salamat po',
        'magandang umaga',
        'mahal kita',
        'kumusta ka',
      ],
      'correctAnswer': 'kumusta ka',
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin words to form the sentence "Magandang gabi" (Good evening)',
      'options': ['ᜄᜈ᜔', 'ᜋ', 'ᜊᜒ', 'ᜄ', 'ᜇᜅ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ᜋ', 'ᜄᜈ᜔', 'ᜇᜅ᜔', 'ᜄ', 'ᜊᜒ'],
    },
        {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Baybayin words to form the sentence "Magandang umaga" (Good morning)',
      'options': ['ᜄᜈ᜔', 'ᜋ', 'ᜄ', 'ᜂ', 'ᜋ', 'ᜇᜅ᜔'],
      'correctAnswer':['ᜋ', 'ᜄᜈ᜔', 'ᜇᜅ᜔', 'ᜂ', 'ᜋ', 'ᜄ'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman alphabet words to form the sentence "ᜐᜎᜋᜆ᜔ ᜉᜓ" ',
      'options': ['mat', 'la', 'sa', 'po'],
      'correctAnswer': ['sa', 'la', 'mat', 'po'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'drag_drop',
      'question': 'Arrange these Roman alphabet words to form the sentence "ᜋᜑᜎ᜔ ᜃᜒᜆ" ',
      'options': ['hal', 'ta', 'ki', 'ma'],
      'correctAnswer': ['ma', 'hal', 'ki', 'ta'],
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin sentence for "Ingat ka" (Take care)',
      'character': 'ᜁᜅᜆ᜔ ᜃ',
    },
    {
      'type': 'tracing',
      'question': 'Trace the Baybayin sentence for "Magandang hapon" (Good afternoon)',
      'character': 'ᜋᜄᜈ᜔ᜇᜅ᜔' 'ᜑᜉᜓᜈ᜔',
    },
  ];
  
  static final List<List<Map<String, dynamic>>> allLevels = [
    baybayinCharacters,
    twoSyllableWords,
    threeSyllableWords,
    fourSyllableWords,
    fiveSyllableWords,
    sentences,
  ];
}